informationcrawler.com 2008-09-23

# Information Crawler

__**Privacy Policy**__

Information Crawler, Inc. ("Information Crawler") has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our visitors and customers (each a "User" or "you"). The following discloses our information gathering, use and dissemination practices for www.softwareenterprise.com (the "Site").   
1\. Personal and Non-Personal Information When visiting the Site, in order to become a member, make a purchase, register to use certain services, respond to a survey or update your information, you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address, physical address, telephone number, or credit card number ("Personal Information"). You may review and revise any Personal Information we have about you. 

In addition, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as IP host address, pages viewed, search queries, advertisement impressions and other data ("Aggregate Information"). Permanently stored Aggregate Information is stored separate and apart from Personal Information. 

2\. Information Usage We use Personal Information to enable and enhance User services and to contact a User when necessary, such as to verify downloads, uploads or payment information. Information Crawler may also use this information to notify Users about new products or services and special promotions offered by Information Crawler. Information Crawler will only share Personal Information with third parties pursuant to a User's stated preferences, or as necessary to provide services utilized by you on the Site, such as credit card processing. 

We may use Aggregate Information to improve and enhance your experience on the Site. For example, we may use certain preferences you provide to tailor your experience at our Site, such as showing you content and sending you notices concerning products and services that may interest you. We may also share this Aggregate Information with other unaffiliated third parties, such as advertisers interested in advertising on the Site or business partners, in an aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the shared information will not contain nor be linked to any Personal Information. Information Crawler will never sell your Personal Information, including your credit card information, to an unaffiliated third party without your consent except in connection with the sale or merger Information Crawler or the Information Crawler division responsible for the such services. 

3\. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act 

Information Crawler does not target its services and does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. 

4\. Changes to policy; Opt-Out Process 

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If at any time in the future we plan to use Personal Information in a way which differs from this policy, we will post such changes at http://www.softwareenterprise.com/privacy.html and provide you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of any changes to these terms means you accept these changes. 

5\. Cookies "Cookies" are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. Many web sites use cookies for these purposes. 

We may use cookies (a) to customize your visit to the Site and your experience, (b) to deliver content consistent with your stated interests and the manner in which you browse and/or buy on our Site, (c) to save your login information (if you have registered with us) so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our Site, and (d) for other purposes to make your visit more convenient or to enable us to enhance our service. 

At times, some of our third party advertisers or their ad serving and tracking providers may place cookies on your computer system when you select their ad banners. We have no control over these third party cookies. In addition, Information Crawler may receive some of the data collected by those third party cookies in order to understand how you use the Internet and what products are of interest to you. The information that we receive from these third parties is only Aggregate Information. Information Crawler is not able to control the cookie or other information practices of third parties if you use any peer-to-peer services accessible through the Site. 

You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Site, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. Information Crawler does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer for purposes that are unrelated to the Site or your interaction with the Site. 

6\. Internet Protocol (IP) Address 

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. Your IP address may also be used to help identify you and your shopping cart for the duration of a session and to gather broad demographic information. Your IP address will never be linked to any of your Personal Information unless you are in the process of making a purchase, in which case the link between this information will terminate upon completion of your final purchase. 

7\. Clickstream 

As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as "clickstream data," can be collected and stored by a web site's server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use, the address of the web site from which you linked to the Site, and, in some instances, your e-mail address. We may use clickstream data as a form of Aggregate Information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of our Site, how visitors navigate throughout the Site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information will only be used to improve our Site. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregate, and will not contain any Personal Information. 

8\. Consent to Processing 

By providing any Personal Information to this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, usage and processing of such information in the United States. 

9\. Other Sites 

Our Site may contain links to other sites or provide access to peer-to-peer services. Other sites may also reference or link to our Site. Information Crawler encourages Users to be aware when they leave our Site or access peer-to-peer services and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that you visit. Information Crawler is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites or peer-to-peer activities. 

10\. Security 

The security of your Personal Information is very important to us. We attempt to provide for the secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers by utilizing encryption software. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and Information Crawler, and Information Crawler and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers and your use of the Site demonstrates your assumption of this risk. Only those Information Crawler employees who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed access to your Personal Information. 

11\. Your Acceptance of this Policy 

By using this Site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this policy, please do not use the Site. 

12\. Contact 

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, Information Crawler can be contacted at: support@thesoftwareobjects.com.
